medbroadcast.com 2017-12-01

# MediResource Privacy Policy - About - MedBroadcast.com

**Welcome**

This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you of practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, before using or submitting information to this site. Please note: This site is intended for use by residents of Canada.

**Your Consent**

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information, personal or otherwise, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

You can withdraw your consent for the use of identifiable information, like an email address, by unsubscribing from the service for which you provided that information.

Please be advised that this site makes every effort to protect your personal information and abides by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (also known as PIPEDA), which requires that consent be obtained in all instances where personal information is requested.

**What is "Personal Information"?**

Simply stated, personal information is factual information that is not already available in a public directory, such as a telephone book; or on your business card. Examples of personal information include age, full name, weight, height, medical records, ID numbers (driver's license, health card), ethnic origin, or blood type.

**About Children**

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Websites.

**Active Information Collection**

Like many websites, this site actively collects information from its visitors both by asking specific questions and by permitting them to communicate directly with us via email, feedback forms, and/or discussion boards. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, email address, phone number, and so on). Some areas of this site may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, order processing) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes or other promotions). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional. Links or reference to this privacy policy will be made available at such collection points.

**Passive Information Collection**

As you navigate through a Website, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection. We use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses on this site. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider so you can access the Internet; it is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user's computer). We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and administer and improve the site. 

A "cookie" is information that a Web site sends to your Web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences. "Session" cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased upon closing your Web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on Web sites and to collect aggregate statistical information. This site uses session cookies. "Persistent" cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (e.g., passwords), helping to determine what areas of the Web site visitors find most valuable, and customizing the Web site based on your preferences. This site uses persistent cookies. 

We work with partners who collect preference data through the use of "third-party cookies". Third-party cookies collect anonymous pieces of information about you based on your use of our site. Anonymous information may include things such as which pages you viewed, how much time you spent on the site, or which country you visited from. This anonymous information does NOT contain any personally identifiable information ("PII") about you. Personally identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, social security number or e-mail address is NOT collected through the third-party cookies used on this site. The anonymous information collected through third-party cookies is used by our partners to provide a more targeted advertising experience both on and off our websites. This is known as Interest-Based Advertising. With this type of advertising, companies and advertisers try to predict what ads might be the most interesting to you based on your anonymous preference data. Interest Based Advertising helps support sites you visit to provide free content and helps advertisers reach the right people for their products and services. 

You, as a consumer, have several choices to control the collection and use of information about your web browsing activities. There are two ways a user can opt-out of the collection and usage of anonymous information through third-party cookies: 

  1. Block all cookies by globally or selectively disabling cookie use in your browser configuration. 
  2. Use one of the opt-out tools below to opt-out of interest-based advertising from third party members belonging to the self-regulatory associations below: 
    * Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) opt-out tool: [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)
    * Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt-out tool: [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
    * Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (DAAC) opt-out tool: [youradchoices.ca/choices](http://youradchoices.ca/choices)
    * European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA’s) opt-out tool: [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

You may also find more information about entities involved in online advertising and additional choices you may make through the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") at the [NAI Service](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) (the "DAA") at the [DAA consumer choice Service](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

"Internet tags" (also known as single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1-by-1 GIFs) are smaller than cookies and tell the Web site server information such as the IP address and browser type related to the visitor's computer. We use Internet tags at this site. Tags have been placed both on online advertisements that bring people to the site and on different pages of the site. These tags indicate how many times a page is opened and which information is consulted. We do not collect or seek personally identifiable information through these tags. 

"Navigational data" ("log files", "server logs", and "clickstream" data) are used for system management, to improve the content of the site for market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. This site uses navigational data.

We are using Google Analytics cookies and have enabled the [Demographics and Interest Reporting](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2799357) which provides us with data from Google's Interest-based advertising and 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests). This feature allows us to better evaluate who our users are, how their behaviour varies by demographics and interests, and ultimately help us create more appropriate content for our users. You can choose to opt-out of this feature using [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

We follow industry privacy standards for online advertising. The advertisements displayed on our websites are served through one or more reputable third party advertisement-serving companies, including Google. We are using Google Adsense cookies. You can control advertising cookies from Google by using its Ad Preferences Manager, available here: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you control cookies from being put on your computer by other companies you can visit <http://youradchoices.ca/>.

We also use the Sovrn third party ad network to serve ads on our site and are using the Sovrn cookies. If you are interested in more information about the Sovrn ad network you can visit <http://www.sovrn.com/>.

**Use and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise stated, we may use your information to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you, for our marketing and research purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy. If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We will take reasonable measures to prevent personally identifiable information from being combined with passively collected information, unless you consent otherwise. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to our affiliates that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties, but only: 

  1. to contractors we use to support our business (e.g., fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy;
  2. in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or
  3. where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.

In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not deemed personally identifiable. 

**Access and Correction**

To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you have previously submitted via this site. 

**Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Moreover, when using passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features, on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them. 

**Links to Other Websites**

This site may contain links or references to other Websites. Please be aware that we do not control other Websites and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those Websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every Website you visit.

**Social Media**

This site has a number of social media tools (Reddit, Digg, Facebook "like" button, etc). By clicking on these tools, you are sharing information on those sites. Those sites may have different privacy policies than this one. You should be aware of these policies before you use these tools.

**Other Terms**

Your use of this site is subject to our Terms and Conditions. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, please contact us as follows: 

[privacyofficer@mediresource.com](mailto:privacyofficer@mediresource.com?subject=Contact%20Privacy%20Officer%20at%20MediResource.com) or  
webmaster@mediresource.com

MediResource Inc.  
789 Don Mills Road, Suite 400  
Toronto, Ontario  
M3C 1T5  
416-383-0010 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 19, 2017.
